[{"answer": "Well, it's a bit surreal for sure because, I mean, I think controversial more than notorious.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "How do you feel about this extraordinary mayhem erupting around you, your story, this movie?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I guess for me, I -- it's important that the movie is viewed the right way certainly as a cautionary tale.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "What is the real message you want to get out?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "It was amazing.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "And what did make you feel like to see DiCaprio do that?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "I spent a lot.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "How much time did you spend with Leo DiCaprio?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "You know, countless hours, you know, hundreds of hours.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Yeah, or hundred plus hours.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "Hundreds of hours in his company?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Oh, either, you know, by telephone in my house or his house or out somewhere.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "And how did you find him and how did he find you when you were just interacting together?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "You know it was shocking.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "When you watched the movie, what did you feel about the reality because only you would know really?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "In a -- in a good way.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "In a good or bad way?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "True.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "A female employee shaved her head for $10,000 in front of the paying morbid (ph) stuff, true?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Yes, yes and if they -- I guess that the philosophy was, you know, her hair will grow back and then it would all be perfect in six months.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "To get breast implant, she shaved her head for $10,000?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Well, you become numb and that's what happened with insanity and all the sort of stuff that you do where what seems amazing at first becomes complex after a while.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "$50?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "I wasn't there at that time.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Did that happen?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "After I left, yes, yes.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "But you heard it happened?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "It happened.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Your number two portrayed in the movie by Jonah Hill ate a live goldfish that belong to a Sratton Oakmont, the firm employee, did that happen?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "You saw him do that?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "It's a guy named Danny.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "So the real-life guy is who really?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "He ate the goldfish though, yes, and he has publicly admitted that and ...", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "But did Danny eat the goldfish?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "It kind of nadir (ph) of croaking (ph) excess, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "I think it -- I think that sort of behavior isn't just endemic to Wall Street.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "It's about who can go the furthest?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Not mail because they have like -- people had pets in the office.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "Did you have a chimpanzee in the office handing out mail?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "ELFORT: I don't know.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "You kind of thinking this is perfectly normal?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "It had to do with in act of sexual deprave view.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "Can you give me a clue?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "A bit of embarrassment, and you know, putting on brave face maybe.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Well, how would you categorize it?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Not -- it's not -- shame is the wrong word.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Do you feel shame?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "The first time is -- it really started in the meat business.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "When was it you realized you have this ability to sell?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Yeah, I bailed.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "They want a dental school and you bail?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "I, yeah -- I've really, you know, I always want to be rich.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Because I have apparently guys and you couldn't make -- you couldn't rich too, right?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "You actually made yourself bankrupt?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "And I'm like, \"This is it.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Do you think you missed this?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Yes, the firm.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "When you say over meaning was it -- didn't the firm went on?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Besides they cure cancer that's the problem.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "They cure cancer?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Well, you know, one of the important distinctions I think is the people to know you, especially young people, is that in the movie when I walk into the firm and I get my first look at it, and I sit down.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "And what do you realize in that moment?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "No, not quite.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "Is that what happened in real life?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "About two -- I would say about a month in -- I totally got what's going on.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "When did you realize it wasn't what it seemed?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "It was -- there was a series of moments.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "And is that the ethical moment for you when you crossed the line?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "I would say 90 percent was legal in terms of the data it operates, 95 probably, but the five percent was incredibly destructive, and disgusting, and poisoned, everything else.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "When it became as big firm, Stratton Oakmont, and you were making millions and millions and millions, how much of it do you think -- looking back of it, and be completely honest here because you have been about many things, how much of it was legal and how much of it was illegal?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "And you knew that was all happening?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Well, I think that what happened was is that when you get into this section of Wall Street, it's very easy just sort of rationalizing what you're doing and I rationalized each of my actions one step at a time.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Why did you become this art criminal?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Is that they didn't do it.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "And what's the easy answer?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "You know, I think that's -- it's hard to say because I think that I got to a point in my life where I was probably about as awful as a person as I was capable of being and still walking around.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Did you lose your soul completely?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Are you surprised more people in Wall Street haven't gone to prison since the financial crash that we all went through?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "About 12.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "As of now, you've paid back how much?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Do you have any expectation or hope you'll ever get to pay them all back?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "That's not right.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Is that not right anymore?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Yes, for I was on probation.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Was there ever the case?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "I'm giving 100 percent of both books, everything, and the movie.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "But are you continuing to do that?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Because we we're calling rich people.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Why is that not true?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "That you were deliberately...", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "I don't know anyone who lost their life savings.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Well, some of them did, right?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "I think it's terrible.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "... in some cases, having their lives completely turned upside down?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "I have not.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Have you met one of your victims?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "No one just sought me out.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "You know, I don't want to intrude anybody's life and you know...", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Why haven't you sought them out?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "Oh Piers, I think it's a very good point you're bringing up.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "But have you ever seen them as human beings or it's part of the issue with the kind of culture that we see in the movie that actually in the end you become suddenly dehumanized?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "If you found them, oh yeah, sure I would.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "If I found a few of your victims, would you come and see them?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "Possibly.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Is that what you're saying?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "Well, again I..", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "What about somebody losing half their life savings like the guy I read out, Peter Springsteel?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "My parents?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "No judgment.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "What else did she say to you?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "No criticism?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "Similar.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Your father, what did he say?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "You know it's -- I think for me I'm in a place in my life right now where my -- the business I'm in right now where I go around the world doing seminars, and sales training, and motivations, stuff like that, and entrepreneurship -- I know in my heart that what I'm doing is pure and it's great and it's empowering.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "How best to deal with the feelings you may have of the old Jordan Belfort?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "An incredible acting.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "And as scene in the movie, this memorable scene where Leo DiCaprio taking too many quellos (ph) and just basically disintegrating before our very eyes which happened, right?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "I think the lowest moment for me was not getting arrested.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "Was it the balloon going up, being arrested, was it the court case, was it going to prison, was it the first night in prison, what was the absolute lowest moment for you?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "I know I was an amazing father and I'm proud of that.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 671, "question": "Bad father?", "qSentId": 670}, {"answer": "Oh, I mean listen I had a -- I got sober when my daughter was three and my son was one.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "Always an amazing father?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "I was really, really close.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "What's your relationship with them like now?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "It was -- and it's good question.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "What did they think of the movie?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "Well, we had a struggle on the stairs.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "Did you hit her at all?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "Obviously, I mean look my children have seen me come back from jail and all that to build this new life.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "When you took your ex-wife and your kid to the cinema to watch the movie, you're about to finish that story, how did they feel?", "qSentId": 698}, {"answer": "It's not true.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "A tweet here from Sam Gustin in Time Magazine, a critical unanswered question comment on depiction that he remained on SCC deal, why do you that if true?", "qSentId": 716}, {"answer": "It changed -- it wasn't like that really.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "But it wasn't about that?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "Not Steve Madden at all.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 732, "question": "Did you feel guilt about all the people he went to prison because you basically wiped yourself up and ratted on him?", "qSentId": 731}, {"answer": "I haven't.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 736, "question": "Have you spoken to him since?", "qSentId": 735}, {"answer": "It's a good question and there's two sides to that coin because, you know, what do you -- the part of that says, \"Well, I'm supposed to do the right thing and be an upstanding citizen and as crimes committed I should help bring those people to justice.\"", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 741, "question": "How do you feel about that now?", "qSentId": 740}, {"answer": "I think the way I split that was in the movie.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 747, "question": "Could you do the same again?", "qSentId": 746}, {"answer": "It's not that I don't have regrets, of course I have regrets about it but I think I made -- I know that I made the right decision morally and unethically.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 758, "question": "No regrets?", "qSentId": 757}, {"answer": "I'm on the pen for three months.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 768, "question": "So the best thing to say is I would say to you, \"Piers, how long have you been in the market for a pen?", "qSentId": 767}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 770, "question": "I see you're looking for a pen for three months now?", "qSentId": 769}, {"answer": "I like a nice easy to use ballpoint pen or something.", "docId": "140124pmt", "aSentId": 773, "question": "And what type of pens do you typically use when you use a pen?", "qSentId": 772}]